What do you do with old stuff?
旧物该怎么处理？
That top you bought for a party three years ago, for example. You wore it once and it's been hanging in your wardrobe ever since.
比如三年前为派对买的那件上衣，你只穿过一次，之后就一直挂在衣柜里。
You could throw it away, but that seems wasteful – after all it's still perfectly usable.
你可以扔掉它，但这似乎很浪费——毕竟它完全能穿。
So, what to do?
那该怎么办呢？
In the UK, we might take it to a charity shop.
在英国，人们可能会把它送到慈善商店。
The first charity shops appeared in Britain in the 19th Century.
英国最早的慈善商店出现在19世纪。
The Salvation Army, a UK charity, was one of the first to run a second-hand clothing shop to provide the impoverished and needy with affordable clothes.
英国慈善机构“救世军”是最早经营二手服装店的机构之一，旨在为贫困和有需要的人提供价格实惠的衣物。
This was followed by charities such as the British Red Cross, who also relieved hardship and raised money for the war effort during World War Two.
随后，英国红十字会等慈善机构也加入其中，它们在二战期间还通过这种方式摆脱贫困带来困难并为战争筹集资金。
The modern form we know today was opened in 1947 by Oxfam.
我们如今熟知的现代慈善商店形式由乐施会于1947年开创。
These days, charity shops are a common sight with around 11,200 shops across the UK, according to the Charity Retail Association.
据慈善零售协会数据，如今慈善商店在英国随处可见，全国约有11200家。
During business hours any member of the public can donate their unwanted items to a charity shop – clothes, books, electronics, furniture. Most charity shops will take anything.
在营业时间内，任何公众都可以将不需要的物品捐赠给慈善商店——衣物、书籍、电子产品、家具等，大多数慈善商店几乎接受任何物品。
These items are checked for wear and tear and if found still serviceable, priced up to be sold at a heavily discounted price.
这些物品会被检查是否有磨损，若仍可使用，就会定价并以大幅折扣出售。
For many, this is a win-win situation.
对许多人来说，这是双赢。
To the charity, it means a valuable source of revenue, which they can use to pursue their charitable aim. To the consumer, it provides the opportunity to buy, often extremely cheaply, items and clothes. Though previously owned, they are durable. To the donator, it declutters and may help to assuage consumer guilt.
对慈善机构而言，这是宝贵的收入来源，可用于实现其慈善目标；对消费者而言，这提供了以极低价格购买物品和衣物的机会，这些物品虽为二手，但依然耐用；对捐赠者而言，这能清理杂物，并有助于减轻消费内疚感。
“You can make a pretty good case to yourself that you are doing good, because what you are doing is going towards a charitable cause [and] you are saving stuff from landfill,” Clare Press, fashion journalist and sustainable style advocate, tells the Guardian.
时尚记者兼可持续时尚倡导者克莱尔・普雷斯在接受《卫报》采访时表示：“你可以说服自己正在做善事，因为你所做的事既支持了慈善事业，又避免了物品被扔进landfill（垃圾填埋场）。”
Indeed, approximately £140 million worth of clothing alone goes into landfill each year, according to UK charity WRAP, the Waste and Resources Action Programme.
事实上，据英国慈善机构“废弃物与资源行动计划”（WRAP）统计，仅衣物一项，每年就有约1.4亿英镑的衣物被扔进垃圾填埋场。
There are sometimes hidden treasures for the buyers, too.
对买家而言，有时还能发现隐藏的宝藏。
On more than one occasion a buyer has purchased something very cheaply, only to later discover its true value – such as a screen print bought for 99p and later found to be by English artist Ben Nicholson. It sold at auction for £4,200.
不止一次，有人以极低价格购得物品，后来却发现其真正价值——例如一幅以99便士购得的丝网印刷品，后来被认定为英国艺术家本・尼科尔森的作品，最终在拍卖会上以4200英镑售出。
So next time you need to rid yourself of something, spare a thought for the charity shop – after all, charity begins at home!
因此，下次你想处理物品时，不妨想想慈善商店——毕竟，慈善始于自家！